Finding Aid for Walter Drew Papers 1900-1961
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Topical files
  - National Erectors' Association
    - Executive Committee, election to
      - 1951-1956 (Reel 31)
    - Finance Committee (Reel 31)
    - Membership correspondence
      - 1906-1926 (Reel 31)
      - 1927-1952 (Reel 32)
    - Membership lists (Reel 32)
    - Membership withdrawals (Reel 32)
    - Miscellaneous (Reel 32)
  - National Guard (Reel 32)
  - National Industrial Conference Board
    - Correspondence
      - 1908-1928 (Reel 32)
    - Literature (Reel 32)
    - Minutes and proceedings (Reel 32)
  - National Industrial Recovery Act (Reel 33)
  - National Labor Relations Act
    - 1934-1935 (Reel 33)
    - 1936-1946 proposed amendments (Reel 33)
  - National War Labor Board, structural iron workers case 1917-1921 (Reel 33)
  - New Jersey (Reel 34)
  - Newark, New Jersey (Reel 34)
  - New Haven, Connecticut (Reel 34)
  - Newspaper clippings
    - 1921 (Reel 34)
    - 1923-1925 (Reel 34)
    - 1927 (Reel 34)
    - 1930-1935 (Reel 34)
    - 1939 (Reel 34)
  - New York (city) Building Trades (Reel 34)
  - New York (city) District Council, United Housesmiths and Bridgemen's Union (Reel 34)
  - Omaha, Nebraska (Reel 34)
  - Open Shop
    - Correspondence, general
      - 1909 (Reel 34)
      - 1920-1923 (Reel 34)
    - Correspondence re. open shop debates 1913-1921 (Reel 34)
    - Literature (Reel 35)
    - National Association of Manufacturers (Reel 35)
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, San Francisco, California (Reel 35)
  - Parks, Sam, trial of 1903 (Reel 35)
  - Pension plans (Reel 35)
  - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania (Reel 35)
  - Picketing (Reel 35)
  - Pirie, S.C. 1918 (Reel 35)
  - Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania (Reel 35)
  - Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania Post Office (Reel 36)
  - Plays (Reel 36)
  - Political material (Reel 36)
  - Portland Cement Association (Reel 36)
  - The President's Industrial Conference 1920 (Reel 36)
  - Prevailing rate of wages law
    - 1921-1935 (Reel 36)
  - Prevailing rate of wages litigation, James J. Ryan v. Edward Kloberg, Inc., New York City 1934 (Reel 36)
  - Profit sharing (Reel 36)
  - Propaganda against unions (Reel 37)
  - Providence, Rhode Island (Reel 37)
  - Public and Employees Relations News (Reel 37)
  - Public Works (Reel 37)
  - Publicity re. dynamitings and assaults (Reel 37)
  - Publications, correspondence with
    - Buffalo Commercial (Reel 37)
    - Detroit Saturday Night (Reel 37)
    - Miscellaneous
      - 1907-1934 (Reel 37)
    - New York Times (Reel 37)
    - Richmond News Leader (Reel 37)
    - The Trend (Reel 37)
    - Wall Street Journal (Reel 37)
  - Railroads (Reel 38)
    - 1911-1923 (Reel 38)
  - Reconstruction Finance Corporation (Reel 38)
  - Recovery (Reel 38)
  - Restriction of output (Reel 38)
  - Right to Work Commission (Reel 39)
  - Right to Work Laws (Reel 39)
  - San Francisco, California (Reel 39)
  - San Francisco, California, bridge construction 1934 (Reel 39)
  - Sargent, Noel (Reel 39)
  - Secret Strike Ballot (Reel 39)
  - Sherer, R.P. (Reel 39)
  - Shirley, C.C. (Reel 39)
  - Shop men (Reel 39)
  - Slattery, Thomas (Reel 39)
  - Southern Pacific Railway Company, San Antonio Explosion
    - Foster Agency operatives
      - Reports (Reel 40)
      - Union documents copied or obtained 1911-1912 (Reel 40)
    - Foster Agency information re. overall campaign (Reel 40)
  - Steel Erection projects, various cities 1921-1930 (Reel 40)
  - Steel Fabricators of the United States (Reel 40)
  - Strikes
    - Government projects (Reel 41)
      (not filmed)
    - Michigan motor industry: Ford, Hudson, and Briggs (Reel 41)
    - Milwaukee, Wisconsin (Reel 41)
    - Miscellaneous (Reel 41)
    - New York City 1924 (Reel 41)
    - New York City, mid-town tunnel (Reel 41)
    - San Francisco 1934 (Reel 41)
  - Structural Steel Board of Trade (Reel 41)
  - Structural Steel Society (Reel 41)
  - Systems Company (Reel 41)
  - Taft-Hartley Act (Reel 41)
  - Unemployment (Reel 42)
  - Union label on printing (Reel 42)
  - United States Commission on Industrial Relations (Reel 42)
  - United States Steel Corporation (Reel 42)
  - Unlawful activities of unions (Reel 42)
  - Wages (Reel 42)
  - Walsh, Frank: methods of publicity (Reel 42)
  - Willard, Daniel (Reel 42)
  - Wilmington, Delaware (Reel 42)
  - Winter, Ferdinand (Reel 42)
  - Wolman, Leo (Reel 42)
  - Youngstown, Ohio (Reel 42)
- Special files
  Within the Special Files, on Rolls 43-73, are nine subjects. These are James A. Emery, Robert J. Foster, IABSIW, Iron League of New Jersey, S.P. Mitchell, Pennsylvania Railroad case, personal material relating to Drew, Remington Rand Corporation, and U.S. v. Ryan.
  The most interesting historical material is found within the IABSIW files. As part of his effort to obtain evidence against the union, Foster gained admission to the union's international headquarters and removed large quantities of correspondence. Photographic copies of many, if not all, of the letters were retained by Drew, and make up this file.
  Much of the material seized by Foster appeared as evidence in U.S. v. Ryan. Drew's file on the subject included a number of pre-trial statements solicited to supplement the written record and also a virtually complete daily transcript of the trial itself. Drew personally gave testimony on October 25, 1912 (found on Roll 64).
  Robert J. Foster's critical role in Drew's investigations is documented in his section of the special files. Foster's file consists of a lengthy typescript autobiography, which is particularly interesting because of its frankness.
  Drew was strongly attracted to the labor policies of the Remington Rand Company. He followed the 1936 strike against the company very closely. He collected several detailed scrapbooks of newspaper clippings, arranged chronologically, giving an excellent day-by-day account of events. He also obtained a number of company documents, including information regarding labor relations subsequent to the strike.
  In general, Drew's personal material is of limited value. His financial materials were not microfilmed: student account books, ca. 1892, and account books and ledgers, 1906-1917 (these are located in Box 1). His scrapbooks, however, are an exception to this generalization. Drew inserted a great deal of primary material into the scrapbooks, including some correspondence, the text of several speeches he made, and copies of works published by him.
  As a close friend of James A. Emery, a leading NAM spokesman, Drew collected a small body of material about him. Most interesting is a group of speeches and other public papers issued by Emery. Drew also obtained the files of Emery's final project, a history of NAM. Apparently Emery died before he could complete the necessary research.
  Material relating to the Iron League of New Jersey documents membership in the League and the League's relationship with the local unions. Materials relating to the Pennsylvania Railroad case are apparently the files Drew created in his fruitless attempt to obtain numerous indictments. The S.P. Mitchell material consists of an isolated letterbook.
  - James A. Emery (NAM spokesman)
    - Speeches and other public papers
      - Undated (Reel 43)
      - 1908-1934 (Reel 43)
      - 1935-1946 (Reel 44)
    - Proposed History of National Association of Manufacturers circa 1949
      - Accident prevention (Reel 44)
      - Child labor amendment (Reel 44)
      - Conventions (Reel 44)
      - Coonley, Howard (Reel 44)
      - Emery, James "Early Professional Experience" (Reel 44)
      - Federal licensing (Reel 44)
      - Founding and early years (Reel 44)
      - Investigation (Reel 44)
      - Jordan, Virgil (Reel 45)
      - Labor relations (Reel 45)
      - Miscellaneous (Reel 45)
      - Mulhall inquiry (Reel 45)
      - National Labor Relations Act (Reel 45)
      - Post, C.W. (Reel 45)
      - Railway disputes (Reel 45)
      - Tariff policy (Reel 45)
    - Personal correspondence
      - 1910-1963 (Reel 45)
  - Foster, Robert J.
    - Autobiography, Volumes 1-4 (Reel 45)
  - International Association of Bridge and Structural Iron Workers (IABSIW)
    - Correspondence
      - February 1905-August 1908 (Reel 46)
      - September 1908-May 1910 (Reel 47)
      - June 1910-October 1911 (Reel 48)
    - Miscellaneous (Reel 48)
  - Iron League of New Jersey
    - Brandle, T.M. (Reel 49)
    - Charter, by-laws, etc. (Reel 49)
    - Clippings (Reel 49)
    - Department of Justice (U.S. Government) (Reel 49)
    - Interviews, statements, etc. (Reel 49)
    - Membership information (Reel 49)
    - Miscellaneous
      - 1926-1933 (Reel 49)
  - Mitchell, S.P.
    - Letterbook 1903-1906 (Reel 49)
  - Pennsylvania Railroad Case
    - Information file
      - Booklets (Reel 50)
      - Bowen, B.B. (Reel 50)
      - Bulletins of various railway unions (Reel 50)
      - Burger, A.J. (Reel 50)
      - Ford, Charles P. (Reel 50)
      - Franklin, J.A. (Reel 50)
      - Gompers, Samuel (Reel 50)
      - Good, N.P. (Reel 50)
      - Government (correspondence with attorney general and FBI director) (Reel 50)
      - Green, William (Reel 50)
      - Idar, C.N. (Reel 50)
      - Jeffery, H.S. (Reel 50)
      - Jewell, Bert M. (Reel 50)
      - Johnston, William H. (Reel 50)
      - King, B.W. (Reel 50)
      - Knight, F.H. (Reel 50)
      - McGrath, J.F. (Reel 50)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence (Reel 50)
      - Pan-American Federation of Labor (Reel 50)
      - Railway Brotherhoods
        - Background (Reel 50)
        - Financial (Reel 50)
        - Minutes (Reel 51)
        - Miscellaneous (Reel 51)
      - Richberg, Donald R. (Reel 51)
      - Ryan, Joseph (Reel 51)
      - Ryan, Martin (Reel 51)
      - Scott, John (Reel 51)
      - Spelts, John H. (Reel 51)
      - Thorpe, John T. (Reel 51)
    - Trial exhibits
      - 1 (Reel 52)
      - 3 (Reel 52)
      - 5 (Reel 52)
      - 8 (Reel 52)
      - 17-53 (Reel 52)
      - 55-58 (Reel 52)
      - 60-75 (Reel 52)
      - 77-80 (Reel 52)
      - 82-138 (Reel 52)
      - 143-145 (Reel 52)
      - 148 (Reel 52)
      - 170-173 (Reel 52)
      - 202-204 (Reel 52)
      - 206-217 (Reel 52)
      - B, 1B, 2B (Reel 52)
  - Personal material relating to Drew
    - Senior Law Thesis 1896 (Reel 52)
    - Correspondence with family and friends
      - 1907-1949 (Reel 52)
    - Speeches and publications
      - Articles (Reel 52)
      - Legal briefs (Reel 52)
      - Letters to the editor (Reel 52)
      - Newspaper clippings (Reel 52)
      - Pamphlets (Reel 52)
      - Speeches (Reel 52)
      - Testimony (Reel 52)
      - Sound recording of Walter speaking 1950s-1960s (Box 36)
        (reel-to reel tape compiled in 1962, cassette use copy also available)
    - Personal financial material
      - Student account books circa 1892 (Box 29)
      - Account books 1906-1917 (Box 29)
      - Ledgers 1906-1917 (Box 29)
    - Scrapbooks (Reel 53)
      - High school and college (oversize scrapbook) (Reel 53)
      - 1905-1913 (oversize scrapbook) (Reel 53)
      - 1907-1918 (Reel 53)
      - 1919-1936 (Reel 54)
  - Remington Rand Corporation
    - Strikes
      - Chronology of 1936strike (Reel 54)
      - "Truth Will Out", company publication 1937 (Reel 54)
      - Radio broadcast by Earl Harding July 5, 1936 (Reel 54)
      - Radio publicity on 1947strike (Reel 54)
      - Documents (Reel 54)
      - Clippings (Reel 55)
        - 1936-1940 (Reel 55)
        - 1955 (Reel 55)
      - Scrapbooks 1936 strike (oversize) (Reel 55)
    - Labor relations
      - Mohawk plan (Reel 55)
      - Labor legislation (primarily Taft-Hartley Act) (Reel 55)
      - Earl Harding (personal views) (Reel 55)
    - Correspondence
      - Harding, Earl (Reel 55)
      - Rand, James H., Jr. (Reel 56)
    - Syracuse, N.Y. (Reel 56)
  - U.S. v. Ryan
    - Statements and depositions
      - Baity, Orville E. (Reel 56)
      - Barry, James (Reel 56)
      - Burns, Raymond J. (Reel 56)
      - Burns, William J. (Reel 56)
      - Butler, George (Reel 56)
      - Caldwell, George (Reel 56)
      - Cooke, John B. (Reel 56)
      - Crook, Herbert A. (Reel 56)
      - Davis, George E. (Reel 56)
      - Detch, Albert G. and George C. (Reel 56)
      - Dondono, Joseph A. (Reel 56)
      - Dugan, Patrick (Reel 56)
      - Emmons, Edna (Reel 56)
      - Emmons, O.J. (Reel 56)
      - Harrington, John R. (Reel 56)
      - Lucas, Hugo and W.W. Rhodes and R.R. Johnson (Reel 56)
      - McManigal, Ortie E.
        - Published biography (Reel 56)
        - Original confession transcript April 14, 1911 (Reel 56)
        - Extended statement and collaborating evidence
          - 1st copy (Reel 56)
          - 2nd copy (Reel 57)
        - Statements
          - May 3, 1911, May 11, 1911 (Reel 57)
          - May 12, 1911, May 20, 1911 (Reel 57)
          - June 20, 1911 (Reel 57)
        - Statement with Mrs. D.H. Ingersoll (Reel 57)
      - Marshall, Wallace (Reel 57)
      - Miscellaneous (Reel 57)
      - Pyle, George W. (Reel 57)
      - Smith, Jesse (Reel 57)
      - Von Spreckelsen, Albert (Reel 57)
      - Wise, William (Reel 57)
    - Related cases
      - Massachusetts v. George O'Donnell (1908) (Reel 57)
      - California v. Clarence Darrow (1913) (Reel 58)
      - City of Cleveland v. Roscoe Tombs (ca. 1911) (Reel 58)
      - French Lick (1911) (Reel 58)
      - Los Angeles (1911)
        - Index of testimony (Reel 58)
        - Index of evidence (Reel 58)
        - Miscellaneous (Reel 58)
      - Peoria (1910) (Reel 58)
      - Columbus, Indiana and Omaha, Nebraska (1911) (Reel 58)
      - Von Spreckelsen Case, Indianapolis (1907) (Reel 58)
    - Reports on IABSIW (Reel 58)
    - Indictments (Reel 59)
    - Defendants by geographic location (Reel 60)
    - Brief on proof of official positions held by defendants (Reel 60)
    - Local union rosters (Reel 60)
    - Index of defendants' character witnesses (Reel 60)
    - Memos re. defendants, A-Z (Reel 60)
    - List of depredations (Reel 60)
    - Chronology for transportation of explosives (Reel 60)
    - List of exhibits (Reel 60)
    - Index of testimony (Reel 60)
    - Foster testimony (Reel 60)
    - Judge's remarks at sentencing (Reel 60)
    - Dynamitings since U.S. v. Ryan (Reel 60)
    - Daily Trial Transcripts October 3, 1912-December 26, 1912
      - October 3-9, 1912 (Reel 61)
      - October 10-15, 1912 (Reel 62)
      - October 16-22, 1912 (Reel 63)
      - October 23-26, 1912 (Reel 64)
      - October 28-November 8, 1912 (Reel 65)
      - November 9-15, 1912 (Reel 66)
      - November 16-20, 1912 (Reel 67)
      - November 21-25, 1912 (Reel 68)
      - November 26-29, 1912 (Reel 69)
      - November 30-December 4, 1912 (Reel 70)
      - December 5-9, 1912 (Reel 71)
      - December 10-13, 1912 (Reel 72)
      - December 14-26, 1912 (Reel 73)
- Drew papers collected by Dallas L. Jones
  A small group of material consists of Drew Papers Collected by Professor Dallas L. Jones. Artificially gathered, and located on Roll 74, the papers generally supplement items found in other parts of the collection.
  - Miscellaneous (Reel 74)
- Photographs
  Photographs are also located on Roll 74. There are portraits of Walter Drew as well as pictures of time bombs, damaged steel work, union members, company officials, and convicts, in addition to other miscellaneous items. The original photographs are located in Box 36, along with the sound recording and the personal financial materials.
  - Microfilmed photos
    - Caldwell and Drake, Columbus, Indiana (damage to) (Reel 74)
    - Labor leaders and union members (mug file) (Reel 74)
    - Miscellaneous (Reel 74)
    - Portraits of Walter Drew (Reel 74)
    - "Delegates. Pickets and Characters, Leberman and Sanford, Rubin and Rubin, September-October 1911", 1 album (Reel 74)
    - Damage to steel work at various sites in the U.S., time bombs used, company officials, union members, convicts, police records, hotel records, transportation records, and other court evidence., 1 album (Reel 74)
- Drew Papers
  - Originals of microfilmed papers
    [Boxes 1-35, staff use only, available on microfilm]
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 1)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 2)
      (continued)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 3)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 4)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 5)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 6)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 7)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 8)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 9)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 10)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 11)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 12)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 13)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 14)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 15)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 16)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 17)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 18)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 19)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 20)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 21)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 22)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 23)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 24)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 25)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 26)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 27)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 28)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 29)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 30)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 31)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 32)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 33)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 34)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 35)
    - Originals of microfilmed papers (Box 36)
- Photographs
  (Photographs are included on Reel 74 of microfilm)
  - Caldwell and Drake, Columbus, Indiana (damage to) (Box 36)
  - Labor leaders and union members (mug file) (Box 36)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 36)
  - Portraits of Walter Drew (Box 36)
  - "Delegates. Pickets and Characters, Leberman and Sanford, Rubin and Rubin September-October 1911", 1 album (Box 36)
  - Damage to steel work at various sites in the U.S., time bombs used, company officials, union members, convicts, police records, hotel records, transportation records, and other court evidence, 1 album (Box 36)
- Personal financial material
  (Materials Not Microfilmed)
  - Student account books circa 1892 (Box 36)
    (not filmed; originally in box 29)
  - Account books 1906-1917 (Box 36)
  - Ledgers 1906-1917 (Box 36)
- Sound recording 1950s, 1960s made in 1962
  (A compilation of 8 excerpts of conversations and other events. recorded at various dates on 1 one reel-to reel tape; (also includes cassette copy). According to enclosed note, WD was not aware that he was being taped)
  - Excerpt 1
    - W.D. discussing religion, art, unions, etc. with his family at N.Y. apartment about 1952 (Box 36)
  - Excerpt 2
    - Letters to Sherers -- 1956 (W.D.'s sister & family) (Box 36)
  - Excerpt 3
    - Excerpts from old white wax disc recording
      - W.D., Mrs. Carned (W.D.'s mother in law), Mrs. Drew (Box 36)
      - W.D. calling the housekeeper (Box 36)
      - W.D. at the home of a friend for dinner (Box 36)
      - W.D. tea with Sherers (W.D.'s sister & family) in NY apt. (Box 36)
  - Excerpt 4
    - Conversation of Judge Garnett (Eugene) with Mrs. Drew at NY Apt. (Judge Garnett has one of W.D.'s closest friends & roommate at Michigan). (Box 36)
  - Excerpt 5
    - Concert at home in Conn. discussing voice of Julia Gilbert who had sleeping sickness and voice of Mrs. Drew August 1960 (Box 36)
  - Excerpt 6
    - Mr. & Mrs. Frantz Proschowski for tea at NY apt., W.D. discusses art & painting (Box 36)
  - Excerpt 7
    - Copy of disc recording of Robert J. Foster, close friend of W.D. and worked under him on dynamite cases; he was also private detective (Box 36)
  - Excerpt 8
    - Taped letter from Renslow P. Sherer (W.D.'s Brother-in-law) to W.D. on the labor question (Box 36)
- Topical Files
  (additions to the Walter Drew papers received in 2002 from professor Dallas L. Jones)
  - American Bridge Company 1911-1912 (Box 37)
  - American Federation of Stockholders 1913-1917 (Box 37)
  - Assaults 1907-1932 (Box 37)
  - William J. Burns, Detective 1913 (Box 37)
  - Clarence Darrow Case 1906-1948 (Box 37)
  - Walter Drew
    - Notebook of Correspondence and Speeches 1907-1950 (Box 37)
    - Pamphlets 1908-1947 (Box 37)
    - Scrapbook of Newspaper Clippings 1912-1916, 2 folders (Box 37)
  - Dynamite Case 1906-1932, 2 folders (Box 37)
  - Charles W. Eliot 1910-1923, 3 folders (Box 37)
  - James A. Emery 1910-1969, 3 folders (Box 37)
  - John D. Fredericks 1908-1919, 2 folders (Box 37)
  - Grand Rapids Citizens Alliance 1904-1911 (Box 37)
  - Indianapolis Trial 1911-1947 (Box 37)
  - International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers and Pile Drivers 1906-1950 (Box 37)
  - Investigative and Dictograph Reports 1910-1911 (Box 38)
  - Iron League of Philadelphia 1927 (Box 38)
  - Iron Workers' Union circa 1928 (Box 38)
  - John Kirby, Jr. 1910-1919 (Box 38)
  - Legislation 1903-1915 (Box 38)
  - National Association of Manufacturers and Erectors of Structural Steel and Iron Work 1903-1934, 3 folders (Box 38)
  - National City Bank 1916 (Box 38)
  - National Industrial Conference Board 1918 (Box 38)
  - National Recovery Act 1933-1934 (Box 38)
  - National War Labor Board 1918-1919, 2 folders (Box 38)
  - Open Shop Philosophy 1907-1959, 2 folders (Box 38)
  - H. G. Otis 1910-1914 (Box 38)
  - John F. Perkins 1919 (Box 38)
  - Roscoe Pound 1957 (Box 38)
  - President's Industrial Conference 1919-1924 (Box 38)
  - Publications, Correspondence with 1911-1954 (Box 38)
  - Reports 1911 (Box 38)
  - United States Commission on Industrial Relations
    - Correspondence (Box 39)
    - Testimony
      - Walter Drew 1915 (Box 39)
      - Samuel Gompers and James Emery 1914 (Box 39)
      - Anton Johannsen 1914 (Box 39)
  - War Material 1913-1920 (Box 39)
- Dallas Jones's Background Research
  - Interviews with friends and associates of WD (Box 39)
  - Correspondence
    - Carneal Family 1962-1964 (Box 39)
    - Nell Carneal Drew 1961-1974 (Box 39)
    - General Regarding Walter Drew 1962-1966, 2 folders (Box 39)
  - Notes, 2 folders (Box 39)
  - Photographs
    - Dynamite Case Evidence (Box 39)
    - Walter Drew and Colleagues (Box 39)